<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toulmin&#39;s Schema on Morgen&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/categories/toulmins-schema/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toulmin&#39;s Schema on Morgen&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-toha.github.io/categories/toulmins-schema/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Assumptions of Toulmin&#39;s System</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/introduction/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/introduction/abstract/</guid>
      <description>The Toulmin&amp;rsquo;s system comes from pholosopher Stephen Toulmin.
This system assumes:
that all assertions and assumptions are contestable. that all final verdicts about the persuasiveness of the opposing arguments should be supported by a neutral third party </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Schema: Exercise-01</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-01/</guid>
      <description>Claim: Buy this stereo system Reason: because it has a powerful amplifier. Grounds: comparison showing that the system’s amplifier outperforms others. customer feedback reporting the satisfaction with the system’s amplifier. Specification indicating that the system’s amplifier is powerful. Warrant: Powerful amplifiers make good stereo systems. Backing: evidence showing that powerful amplifiers can deliver more hi-fi music, deliver sound farther, work more efficiently, and enable more equalizer adjustments. Rebutting the reason: unless this system does not have a powerful amplifier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Schema: Exercise-02</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-02/</guid>
      <description>Claim: Practicing the piano is good for kids Reason: because it teaches discipline. Grounds: Examples showing that playing the piano enhance a kid’s discipline. Cases or observation indicating that kids who plays piano behave decently and follow regulations. Statistics revealing that kids who playing better piano behave more disciplined. Warrant: Kids should be taught discipline. An activity that teaches discipline is good. Backing: Arguments showing that disciplined kids have better personal development, have more significant achievement, and establish better rapport with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Schema: Exercise-03</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-03/</guid>
      <description>Claim: Welfare benefits for unwed mothers should not be eliminated Reason: because these benefits are needed to prevent unbearable poverty among our nation’s most helpless citizens. Grounds: statistics reporting that unwed mothers are helpless citizens and suffer poverty. examples showing that welfare benefits prevent unwed mothers from being poor. interviews with unwed mothers indicating that these welfare benefits are necessary and helpful. Warrant: We should prevent poverty among our nation’s most helpless citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Schema: Exercise-04</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-04/</guid>
      <description>Claim: The Endangered Species Act is too stringent Reason: because it severely damages the economy. Grounds: Data showing that the damaged economy is caused by this Act, and the constraints listed in the Act greatly decrease economic benefits. Testimony showing that loosening the act will substantially improve the economy. Testimony from economic experts (e.g., officials, scholars, and commentators) may be authoritative and convincing. We should take their advice if they claim that the economy will improve with a looser act after considering overall situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Schema: Exercise-05</title>
      <link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:03:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/toulmin-system/basic-schema/exercise-05/</guid>
      <description>Claim: Abortion should be legal. Reason: because a woman has the right to control her own body. Grounds: Testimony supporting that abortion represents control of the body. Arguments indicating that abortion is a women’s right Laws that guarantee individual freedom. A list of countries that have already legalized abortion. Warrant: We have the right to control our own bodies. A fetus belongs to a pregnant woman. (surrogate mother?) A pregnant woman has the right to decide the fate of the fetus.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
